<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<mets:mets xsi:schemaLocation="http://www.loc.gov/METS/ http://www.loc.gov/standards/mets/mets.xsd http://www.loc.gov/mods/v3  http://www.loc.gov/standards/mods/v3/mods-3-6.xsd" OBJID="doi:10.17910/B7159Q" TYPE="Databrary Dataset" LABEL="Databrary Project Events">
  <!-- I dont know if Databrary Dataset is a fantastic TYPE, but the project events isn't exactly a dataset-->
  <!--
    [HEADER]
  -->
  <mets:metsHdr CREATEDATE="2015-09-02T17:05:07" LASTMODDATE="2015-09-02T18:25:37">
    <mets:agent ROLE="CREATOR" TYPE="ORGANIZATION"><mets:name>Databrary, New York University</mets:name></mets:agent>
  </metsHdr>
  
  <!--
    [DESCRIPTIVE]
    Defines the study as a whole (the "dataset")
  -->
  <!--This is what it would look like if we wanted to use both MODS and Dublin Core-->
  <mets:dmdSec ID="DM1">
    <mets:mdWrap MDTYPE="MODS">
      <mets:xmlData>
        <mods:mods>
          <mods:titleInfo>
            <mods:title>Databrary Project Events</mods:title>
          </mods:titleInfo>
          <mods:typeOfResource>
            mixed material
          </mods:typeOfResource>
          <mods:abstract>
            Our mission is to promote sharing and reuse of video data. Most developmental scientists rely on video recordings to capture the complexity and richness of behavior. However, researchers rarely share video data, and this has impeded scientific progress. Enabling reuse of video data is essential to increasing openness, maximizing the efficiency of limited resources, and accelerating the pace of discovery in the developmental and learning sciences.

            We aim to provide tools that encourage good data management, facilitate open data sharing, enable discovery, and foster data reuse and integration. We are working to build functionality that allows researchers to organize, store, code, and share identifiable video data and other contextual information about the videos with other researchers through a secure web-based library.

            The Databrary project is dedicated to transforming the culture of developmental science by building a community of researchers committed to open video data sharing, training a new generation of developmental scientists and empowering them with an unprecedented set of tools for discovery, and raising the profile of behavioral science by bolstering interest in and support for scientific research among the general public.
          </mods:abstract>
        </mods:mods>
      </mets:xmlData>
    </mets:mdWrap>
  </mets:dmdSec>
  <mets:dmdSec ID="DM2">
    <mets:mdWrap MDTYPE="DC"></mets:mdWrap>
  </mets:dmdSec>
  <!--
    [ADMINISTRATIVE]
    Where is the dataset from and how did it get here? what's happening to it when it's here?
  -->
  <mets:amdSec>

  </mets:amdSec>
  <!--
    [FILE GROUPS]
  -->
  <mets:fileSec>

  </mets:fileSec>

  <!--
    [STRUCTURAL MAP]
  -->
  <mets:structMap>

  </mets:structMap>

  <!--
    [BEHAVIOR]
    unnecessary?
  -->
</mets:mets>